export default data = [
  {
      question: "Since it hasn’t rained for months, there is a water _____ in many parts of the country.",
      options: ["resource","deposit","shortage","formula"],
      correct_option: "shortage"
  },
  {
      question: "The problem with Larry is that he doesn’t know his limitations; he just _____ he can do everything.",
      options: ["convinces","disguises","assumes","evaluates"],
      correct_option: "assumes"
  },
  {
      question: "Agnes seems to have a _____ personality. Almost everyone is immediately attracted to her when they first see her.",
      options: ["clumsy","durable","furious","magnetic"],
      correct_option: "magnetic"
  },
  {
      question: "Jason always _____ in finishing a task no matter how difficult it may be. He hates to quit halfway in anything he does.",
      options: ["persists","motivates","fascinates","sacrifices"],
      correct_option: "persists"
  },
  {
      question: "Poor _____ has caused millions of deaths in developing countries where there is only a limited amount of food.",
      options: ["reputation","nutrition","construction","stimulation"],
      correct_option: "nutrition"
  },
  {
      question: "The helicopters _____ over the sea, looking for the divers who had been missing for more than 30 hours.",
      options: ["tackled","rustled","strolled","hovered"],
      correct_option: "hovered"
  },
  {
      question: "One of the tourist attractions in Japan is its hot spring _____, where guests can enjoy relaxing baths and beautiful views.",
      options: ["resorts","hermits","galleries","faculties"],
      correct_option: "resorts"
  },
  {
      question: "When a young child goes out and commits a crime, it is usually the parents who should be held _____ for the child’s conduct.",
      options: ["eligible","dispensable","credible","accountable"],
      correct_option: "accountable"
  },
  {
      question: "Since you have not decided on the topic of your composition, it’s still ______ to talk about how to write your conclusion. ",
      options: ["preventive","premature","productive","progressive"],
      correct_option: "premature"
  },
  {
      question: "Human rights are fundamental rights to which a person is ________ entitled, that is, rights that she or he is born with.",
      options: ["inherently","imperatively","authentically","alternatively"],
      correct_option: "inherently"
  },
]